<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<FAQs>
  <FAQList id="primary">
    <FAQ id="book-event">
      <summary>How can I book a community event?</summary>
      <description>To book a community event, simply visit the "Event Bookings" section on the portal, select your desired event, and follow the prompts to complete the booking process. You'll receive a confirmation email with event details.</description>
    </FAQ>

    <FAQ id="waste-collection-issue">
      <summary>What should I do if I have a problem with waste collection?</summary>
      <description>If you encounter any issues with waste collection, head to the "Waste Management" section on the portal and fill out the service request form. Our team will get back to you with a resolution as soon as possible.</description>
    </FAQ>

    <FAQ id="submit-feedback">
      <summary>How can I submit feedback about CityLink services?</summary>
      <description>You can submit feedback through the "Feedback" section of the portal. Just fill out the form with your comments or suggestions, and we'll review it to help improve our services.</description>
    </FAQ>

    <FAQ id="access-profile">
      <summary>Can I access my user profile information?</summary>
      <description>Yes, you can access and update your user profile through the "User Profile" section. Here, you can view your contact details, service bookings, and any past feedback you've submitted.</description>
    </FAQ>

    <FAQ id="volunteering-opportunities">
      <summary>Are there any volunteer opportunities available in my community?</summary>
      <description>Yes, we frequently post volunteer opportunities in the "Volunteering Opportunities" section. You can browse through different roles and apply directly through the portal.</description>
    </FAQ>

    <FAQ id="rates-and-taxes">
      <summary>How do I get information about my rates or local taxes?</summary>
      <description>To get information about rates or taxes, visit the "Rates Enquiries" section on the portal. You'll be able to find relevant information about payments, deadlines, and any related inquiries.</description>
    </FAQ>

    <FAQ id="announcements-updates">
      <summary>How can I stay updated on important community announcements?</summary>
      <description>Stay updated by checking the "Public Announcements" section regularly. You can also subscribe to email notifications to receive the latest announcements directly in your inbox.</description>
    </FAQ>

    <FAQ id="service-request-process">
      <summary>What is the process for submitting a service request?</summary>
      <description>To submit a service request, navigate to the "Service Requests" section. Select the type of service you need, fill out the form with your details, and our team will handle your request promptly.</description>
    </FAQ>

    <FAQ id="mobile-friendly">
      <summary>Is the CityLink portal mobile-friendly?</summary>
      <description>Yes, the CityLink portal is fully optimized for mobile use, allowing you to access all services, make bookings, and manage your profile on-the-go.</description>
    </FAQ>

    <FAQ id="update-contact-info">
      <summary>How do I update my personal contact information?</summary>
      <description>To update your personal contact information, log in to your user profile and edit the details under "Account Settings." Your changes will be saved immediately.</description>
    </FAQ>
  </FAQList>
</FAQs>
